http://www.iqchem.com/index.php/privacy-statement

Search ...
Search
HomeCompanyServicesProductsCoatingPlasticsPolymer Soluble DyesInksPartners & AgentsContactNewsIQ GermanyALANTANA
Innovation & Quality in High Value Chemicals
Privacy Statement
We take the protection of natural persons in relation to the processing of personal data seriously. We fully support the principles mentioned in article 5 of the General Data Protection Regulation of the EU (GDPR, (EU) 2016/679) and in particular the prohibition of processing special categories of personal data acc. to art. 9 para. 1 and art. 10 GDPR and the respective regulations regarding personal data in the Swiss Federal Act on Data Protection (FADP). We follow the law as defined in the GDPR and the FADP and the Ordinance pertaining to it (OFADP).To fulfill our obligations with regard to data protection, we limit our activities in connection to our website as follows:- We renounce on analyzing accesses to our website that would allow us  to identify the person accessing the website (e.g. by use of Google  Analytics).- Data related to persons will not be forwarded to any third parties unless  the law requires it or the third party is working for and on behalf of us. - Cookies are used only for technical reasons (in accordance with art. 6,  para. 1, ltr. f GDPR) and not analyzed by us. The visitor of our website may   prevent the installation of cookies by adjusting the settings in his or her   browser.- We renounce on using contact forms in communication via website.We process personal data without the data subject’s explicit consent only in the cases mentioned in art. 6 para. 1 GDPR, as e.g. when needed for the fulfillment of a contract or a legal obligation (ltrs. b and c) or for proportionate purposes of our legitimate interests (ltr. f). Examples for the application of art. 6 para. 1 ltr. f are the use of cookies, Google Maps, and web fonts.The person controlling the adherence to the respective laws: Bruno Piastra, IQChem AG, Benkenstrasse 254, 4108 Witterswil, Switzerland. In accordance with art. 37 GDPR and art. 38 DSAnpUK-EU, there is no data protection officer.Data subjects have all the rights according to art. 7 para. 3, art. 15 to 22, and art. 77 GDPR and the respective rights according to FADP. Personal data are stored for the time needed to fulfill our legal and contractual obligations. External links are made available on our website only to facilitate navigation. We do not assume any responsibility for the respective contents.The content of this website is protected by copyright law.19.7.2018
IQChem Inc.Benkenstrasse 254 CH - 4108 Witterswil
T +41 61 721 95 40info@iqchem.com
ImprintPrivacy Statenment
Copyright © 2018 by IQChem Inc.
Webdesign by Maisfeld Bucher & Paladino
